(Leonard:)She knows I have a girlfriend.
It's so weird.
Oh, my God. You're loving this!
(Leonard:)To my bones.
(Leonard:)I'm not gonna do anything about it.
I love Penny.
(Leonard:)It's just nice to have a young, attractive
woman sniffing around the goods.
(Raj:)I both hate you and want to be you.
This is Ryan Gosling all over again.
Aww. Gentlemen. What is on the
conversational menu this morning?
(Raj:)Leonard stole my woman,
and he knew...
(Raj:)...I was only six to eight months away
from making my move.
(Leonard:)I didn't steal anyone.
(Raj:)Your assistant is totally hitting
on this jerk and he loves it.
Well, that's not acceptable. I'm her boss.
(Sheldon:)She needs to be solely focused
on my needs...
(Sheldon:)...not distracted by your pasty,
androgynous brand of sexuality.
(Leonard:)I'm androgynous?
(Sheldon:)Oh, please. Look at you with your
pouty bee-stung lips.
What do you think I should do?